Welcome to the prayer line section of The Synagogue Church Of All Nations,
where Prophet T.B. Joshua is ministering prayer to the people in Jesus' name.
He ministers prayer to this man, and the man swings out of the prayer line.
Prophet T.B. Joshua stretches forth his hand in Jesus' name, and the man drops to the ground.
This is the power and anointing of our Lord Jesus Christ throwing the man's back straight on the floor.
Wait a minute.
The man slowly rises back up,
and has an intense stare in his eyes.
This is round two.
Prophet T.B. Joshua moves to the right with a kick, and down he goes.
Down on the ground and down for the count.
He did not know what hit him.
This is Jesus Christ in the power of the Holy Spirit.
Do you want to fight me?
Yes.
Who sent you to destroy me?
Who?
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
At the name of Jesus Christ, every spirit must bow.
Rise up, in the name of Jesus!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
The man rises to his feet and the spiritual battle continues.
Your back on the floor!
After the prayer his back is flat on the floor, and then he slithers back up.
Who are you?
You are destroying me!
I'm destroying you?
Yes.
Who are you?
I'm the lion.
The lion?
You want to touch me? OK, touch me if you can touch.
Just touch and see.
The man possessing the spirit of a lion arches his fingers like claws,
and moves forward in an attempt to touch the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
He gets into position and moves closer to grab the man's of God leg.
But look at his hand!
It begins to shake.
Satan's power is powerless in the face of God's armour and weapons.
And down he goes.
The SCOAN Prayer Line
Watch!
Stop that! In the name of Jesus, stop it!
Many of you are toys in their hands.
They can only run from light.
The SCOAN Prayer Line
This is a test of faith.
You can just come and stand in front of him and see whether he will not grab you.
Come and stand in front of him.
The SCOAN Prayer Line
Come.
Watch your screen.
The SCOAN Prayer Line
Don’t touch me, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Get away from me, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Don’t touch me in the name of Jesus Christ!
Leave the place.
The SCOAN Prayer Line
If everyone should meet him, you would be able to know your level,
whom you are in Christ Jesus.
So, do we have a pastor here?
If you are a pastor, please come forward – this is Christianity in practice.
Watch your screen.
This is a practical side of Christianity.
OK
The SCOAN Prayer Line
Give him a mic.
In the name of Jesus!
This is a very practical Christianity.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
In the name of Jesus Christ, out!
Stop that, in the name of Jesus Christ!
The SCOAN Prayer Line
Praying is not saying words.
The power comes in the praying not in saying the words.
Even if everybody here comes together and makes a force,
if that force is in the natural, he will still grab you all together.
He is on the other side.
The SCOAN Prayer Line
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I declare you free!
Contrary spirit, out!
Out!
In Jesus Christ's name!
Watch your screen.
You are free.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Jesus Christ has delivered him, and the spiritual battle is over.
The man looks around strangely as he realizes that the demonic nature and power within,
have been defeated by the mighty power of Jesus Christ.
Emotions begin to flow as Jesus Christ has put an end to his past,
and he is now a new creation in Christ Jesus.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
See him crying.
The demon used his body as a temple.
Why are you crying?
I don’t know where I am.
I thank God for saving me.
Who is Jesus?
He is my Deliverer.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Glory be to God.
Stand up.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
To God be the glory.
Thank You, Jesus!
I am free, in Jesus' name.
TESTIMONY TIME
Here he comes.
Put your hands together for Jesus.
Emmanuel! God is with us. (Matthew 1:23)
My name is Chinedu Nwosu. I come from Abia State, Nigeria.
This is my mum.
I thank God for what He has used Prophet T.B. Joshua to do in my life,
for delivering me from the world of darkness we had gone into.
I was possessed with a demon.
I was a dragon in my world then.
Now, I've been delivered by Prophet T.B. Joshua
into this real world which God has placed me in.
And the powers I had then were so many.
I used those powers to sleep with people.
I would dream. Sometimes, the person would feel that their husband
was having fun with them but he was not.
I'd make the husband be like wood lying in the bed while I had fun with them.
Those are spiritual husbands.
Spiritual husbands come in two ways.
One comes from the marine world where I came from and one comes physically.
Then their husband would be nothing to them anymore.
But I thank God that Prophet T.B. Joshua has delivered me from this world of darkness.
I used the power of lion to put fear in people; they couldn't look at my face.
If they were about 15 to 30 trying to bring me down, I'd bring all of them down because they were nothing.
All of them would be like dead rats in my sight.
I would make sure I pulled every power they had down.
If care was not taken, sorry would be their name.
I would bring them down because the power in me didn’t come from me alone
but from the world of darkness.
If you feel that the world of darkness is not real, the devil is not real - the devil exists.
There is not any other power more than the blood of Jesus Christ.
When I came to The SCOAN, I was at the prayer line and Prophet T.B. Joshua touched me.
When he touched me, it was just like burning fire.
When he came a second time, I couldn't withstand him.
The spirit in me couldn't withstand it.
He asked me if I wanted to fight him and I was bold enough to tell him that I wanted to fight him.
Do you want to fight me?
Yes.
Who sent you to destroy me?
Who?
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Assuming I pulled him down,
that would have been the glory to the kingdom world.
But he beat me to the end.
He made sure that he proved that the blood of Jesus Christ saves.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I declare you free!
Contrary spirit, out!
Out!
In Jesus Christ's name!
Watch your screen.
You are free.
In the end, I was delivered. I was just like a dead lion.
Now at this moment, I give thanks to God because I am back to my original self that I was.
There is something that I saw in the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
There is a great light covering him so I could not hurt him.
The Lord, God Almighty has used Prophet T.B Joshua to deliver me.
I'm free and I'm free forever.
Testimony Time
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
Thank God for saving my son.
My name is Mrs Mercy Nwosu. I am the mother of Chinedu.
My testimony goes like this. Chinedu is my son.
When I gave birth to him, he was a good child.
During his school age years, he was good
but a time came when he started changing from what I used to know him as.
His behaviour turned to something else; nobody was able to look at him.
If he was aggressive, 10 to 15 men could not withhold him.
Even in the school, they called him by the name, 'Ninja'.
I went and reported to the principal and the teachers that they should warn
these children not to be calling my son Ninja because he was behaving abnormally.
Many times, I used to see him act funny and do funny things.
He behaved harshly like a lion as he has confessed.
Everyone in the home used to fear him because of his aggressiveness.
The evil spirit used to come and go. We went to many places for his deliverance.
Many prayer homes, herbalists and many other places but to no avail.
I thank God. Last Sunday, we watched Prophet T.B. Joshua,
live on Emmanuel TV, how God used him to save my son.
Many people even friends and neighbours were around watching live.
Many people gave their lives to Christ on Sunday.
Testimony Time
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the lastest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testmonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 03/04/2019